good morning good afternoon good evening
早上好下午好晚上好
everybody where if you find yourself in
每个人，如果你发现自己
the world my name is Gary Russell I'm
世界，我叫加里·罗素，我是
the current lead on spring integration
当前的Spring 整合领导者
and we're going to talk today it's Bill
今天我们要谈的是比尔
this is an introduction to the DSL but
这是对DSL的介绍，但是
I'm actually going to take a little bit
我实际上要花一点时间
of a deeper dive into what we've
深入了解我们所拥有的
previously exposed just a few links here
以前只在这里公开了一些链接
these slides will be will be shared at
这些幻灯片将在以下位置共享
the end or within when Peter publishes
彼得出版的结尾或结尾
the the video to the blog the home page
视频到博客主页
of the project what's new and a couple
该项目的新增功能和几个
of resources the actual some samples for
资源的实际一些样本
the DSL and of course the link to the
DSL，当然还有到
DSL itself and as I mentioned there's a
DSL本身，正如我提到的，
little bit deeper dive let me just go
更深一点的潜水让我走吧
back and show a little bit of history
返回并显示一点历史
last May we we had a webinar where we
去年五月，我们举行了一个网络研讨会，
introduced the spring integration for oh
介绍了spring的集成哦
release which had been released a few
发布其中已经发布了一些
months earlier and one of the big
几个月前，也是最大的公司之一
additions to spring integration for in
Spring集成中的附加内容
addition to supporting or using the
除了支持或使用
spring messaging module where a lot of
Spring 的消息模块很多
the base classes moved over the spring
春季的基础班
messaging so they could be used in
消息传递，以便可以在
another spring projects such as spring
另一个春季项目，例如春季
WebSockets with spring integration for
具有Spring集成的WebSocket
we added some significant capabilities
我们添加了一些重要功能
to annotation support towards the the
注释对
goal of being able to do spring
能够做 Spring 的目标
integration configuration with Java and
与Java和
and beginning to eliminate the the
并开始消除
requirement for XML some people still
对XML的需求
still prefer to use XML and that's just
仍然更喜欢使用XML，那仅仅是
fine but there are others that prefer to
很好，但是还有其他一些人喜欢
use Java config so in this in this
使用Java配置，因此在此
webinar I talked about the new
我讨论了新的网络研讨会
annotation support that we'd added in
我们添加了注释支持
forw
前叉
and I gave a sneak preview of the of the
我先睹了
Java DSL work that we were doing and the
我们正在做的Java DSL工作以及
project for that for that webinar is is
该网络研讨会的项目是
in the spring integration samples repo
在 Spring Integration 样品仓库中
under the DSL category and it was the
在DSL类别下，它是
spring integration for
Spring Integration
and the information that we talked about
以及我们谈论的信息
in that particular webinar was with two
在那个特定的网络研讨会中，有两个
two versions an annotation version after
两个版本后的注释版本
the the class that we looked at and a
我们看过的课和一个
DSL version as I said that was like a
我说过的DSL版本就像
sneak preview into into what with what
潜入预览
we had planned ahead so that was that
我们已经提前计划了
was last May and then at spring one in
是去年五月，然后在春季
September down in Dallas Texas
九月在德克萨斯州达拉斯市落下
we we took some a deeper dive into
我们更深入地研究了
spring integration configuration using
Spring整合配置使用
the DSL which at that time had been that
当时的DSL
there was a milestone release as well as
有一个里程碑发布以及
a milestone release of spring
Spring 的里程碑式发布
integration for one that particular
集成一个特定的
project built on the the one from the
项目建立在一个
webinar and we actually used we within
网络研讨会，我们实际上是在
that particular talk we progressed from
我们从那个特别的谈话
an XML configured application and ended
XML配置的应用程序并结束
up with with a completely DSL
完全使用DSL
configurator configuration where the
配置器配置在哪里
this application created a it sent an
此应用程序创建了一个，它发送了一个
email so we got a message and we ended
电子邮件，所以我们收到一条消息，我们结束了
up you know doing some header in
你知道在做一些标题
Richmond you can see here start to see
里士满你可以在这里看到开始
some of the DSL flavor here where we
这里有些DSL风格
we're enriching headers and then sending
我们正在丰富标题，然后发送
a message to this this mail I have an
对此邮件的消息我有一个
adapter and similarly in the in the next
适配器，并在下一个中类似
in the next example in that talk we
在那个谈话的下一个例子中，我们
ended up with we received that mail we
最后收到了我们的邮件
again using the DSL from an IMAP idle
再次从空闲的IMAP中使用DSL
adapter we receive the message and you
适配器，我们收到消息，您
know pulled out some headers and stuff
知道掏出一些标题和东西
so that's just a little bit of
所以这只是
background that we did in those two
我们在那两个领域所做的背景
talks and if you go to the the spring
说话，如果你去 Spring
i/o page and to the blog page and search
I / O页面和博客页面并搜索
for these we look for webinar replay
对于这些，我们期待网络研讨会重播
spring integration you'll find you'll
Spring Integration ，你会发现你会
find this one and if you do a search on
找到这个，如果您进行搜索
spring 1/2 GX replay you you'll find
Spring 1/2 GX重播，您会发现
this one so those are those are worth
这个是那些值得的
taking a look at just to see some of the
看看只是看一些
flavors of
的味道
a of what we're what we're going to talk
我们将要谈论的内容
about today a couple of other resources
今天大约还有其他一些资源
that are important we also have online
重要的是我们也在线上
automobile on who's who's a basically a
谁是谁的汽车
major contributor to dare so in fact you
主要贡献者，所以实际上您
know a lot of the initial prototyping
知道很多初始原型
was done by him and he did an awful lot
是他做的，他做了很多事情
of the heavy lifting to make make this
繁重的工作使这
work so we need to give him a shout out
工作，所以我们需要大声喊叫
he actually published a couple of
他实际上出版了几本
tutorials to to show how the DSL can can
教程来展示DSL可以如何
can be used and if we if we take a look
可以使用，如果我们看看
at the we go back to spring integration
在我们回到 Spring Integration
samples repo with anybody that's been
与曾经去过的任何人进行样本回购
around spring integration a long time
围绕 Spring Integration 很长一段时间
one of the initial applications that
最初的应用之一
were the demo applications was this cafe
演示应用程序是这个咖啡馆
application where where the idea is we
应用在哪里我们的主意
get an order in and it gets split into
接到订单，然后分成
order items or drinks which then gets
订购物品或饮料，然后得到
routed to a hot drink and a cold drink
送去喝热饮料和冷饮料
barista to actually prepare the drinks
咖啡师实际准备饮料
they then get aggregated back into a
然后，他们聚合回到一个
delivery and returns so aartsen took
交货和退货，所以aartsen接受了
that cafe sample app and and rewrote it
那个咖啡馆示例应用程序，然后重写
in the DSL and that's in this cafe DSL
在DSL中，在咖啡厅DSL中
the project in the spring integration
Spring Integration 项目
samples Reaper now what he did was take
现在收割的样品是他的工作
take that and then work through line by
接受，然后逐行进行
line I'm not going to go through it here
行，我不会在这里通过它
you can take take it at your leisure you
你可以随便带走
know take a look at a leisure one thing
知道看看休闲一件事
you'll notice is that this is a fairly
您会注意到，这是一个相当
complex flow and we wouldn't necessarily
复杂的流程，我们不一定
answer somebody's pointed out in the
回答某人指出的
comments it's not something we would
评论这不是我们想要的
really recommend making a really complex
真的建议做一个非常复杂的
flow like this using the DSL you take
使用DSL进行这样的流程
tend to split it up this is this dis
倾向于将其拆分，这是此dis
this blog post was really just to
这篇博客文章实际上只是为了
illustrate how the DSL can be used
说明如何使用DSL
you also notice that we're there's an
您还注意到我们在
awful lot of you a extensive use of Java
你们很多人大量使用Java
a lambdas this does make the DSL and
一个lambda，这确实使DSL和
more
更多
easy to look at and to to understand but
易于看和理解，但
obviously there are some people who are
显然有些人
not yet able to move the job at a
尚无法将工作转移到
personally I think the the Lambda
我个人认为Lambda
support is a compelling reason to to
支持是一个令人信服的理由
start looking at movement to job eight
开始看工作八的运动
but in order to accommodate people who
但是为了容纳那些
are not ready to do that yet
还没有准备好这样做
and Artem did a second version of the
而Artem做了第二版的
blog which is using Java six Java 7 that
使用Java六个Java 7的博客
shows how to use the flow using Java 6
显示了如何使用Java 6使用流程
Jonna seven sir
乔娜七先生
yeah and I'll touch on this a little bit
是的，我会讲一点
when when we get into some some live
当我们走进一些现场
demos yeah so so that that's that's the
演示是的，所以那就是
second resource so that through things
第二资源，以便通过事物
that the two webinars or the webinar and
这两个网络研讨会或网络研讨会以及
the spring one two GX talk and the DSL
春季一两GX对话和DSL
line by line discussion now one of the
现在逐行讨论之一
things that will become fairly obvious
事情将变得相当明显
as we as we talk through this some more
当我们谈论更多
today is the DSL currently doesn't
今天是DSL目前还没有
support every every adapter as you know
支持您所知道的每个适配器
for example MQTT is fairly new adapter
例如，MQTT是相当新的适配器
in spring integration we don't have
在 Spring Integration 中，我们没有
direct first-class support in the DSL
DSL中的直接一流支持
but you'll see that that's not really an
但是你会发现那不是真的
entrance because we can really utilize
入口，因为我们可以真正利用
any integration component in the DSL it
DSL中的任何集成组件
just doesn't have what we call
只是没有我们所说的
first-class support and we will see what
一流的支持，我们将看到
I mean by that as a little little time
我的意思是那一点点时间
goes on today so we do have support
今天进行，所以我们有支持
first-class support for for rabbit mqp
对Rabbit MQP的一流支持
events file FTP JDBC JMS mail Mongo and
事件文件FTP JDBC JMS邮件Mongo和
SFTP any of you if you have any
如果您有任何SFTP
preferences oh I really need first-class
喜好哦，我真的需要一流的
support for mqtt then please please
支持mqtt然后请
provide that feedback either through
通过以下方式提供反馈
Stack Overflow using the spring
使用Spring 堆栈溢出
integration tag or or just go ahead and
集成标签，或者只是继续
put something in JIRA to say alright
在JIRA中放点东西好
this would be really cool if I had X and
如果我有X并且这会真的很酷
that's true for really any any feature
几乎任何功能都是如此
requests that you have so let's get
要求您拥有，让我们得到
started with it with a very simple
从一个非常简单的开始
example I just want to just for those
例如我只想为那些
that have seen the earlier presentations
看过较早的演讲
this will be a bit of a recap for people
这将是人们的回顾
that are new to the DSL hopefully this
希望这对DSL来说是新的
will give you a bit of a flavor of what
会给你一点什么味道
we're what we're going to look at so I'm
我们就是我们要看的东西，所以我
going to start off with just going to
从刚开始
write a little J unit test and in this
写一点J单元测试，在这个
case obviously we're not using any Jenny
情况很明显，我们没有使用任何珍妮
XML I'm just going to use the
XML我将使用
configuration class and for convenience
配置类，为方便起见
I'm just going to declare that class as
我将要声明该类为
a as a static class within within this
作为此内的静态类
context and we just resolve this okay so
上下文，我们只要解决这个问题就可以了
the first thing we're going to do is for
我们要做的第一件事是
those unit of the know we annotate a a
那些已知的单位我们会注释aa
Java configuration class with that
Java配置类
configuration that tells the Spring
告诉Spring的配置
Framework that this this class contains
此类包含的框架
bean definitions we have a new
bean定义我们有一个新的
annotation that was that was added in
在其中添加的注释
spring integration for called enable
Spring 集成称为启用
integration now what does that do now
现在集成现在做什么
with the traditional XML application as
与传统的XML应用程序一样
soon as a parser detects that we have a
解析器检测到我们有一个
spring integration component in our
我们的Spring 集成组件
application context the parser causes a
应用程序上下文解析器导致
number of infrastructure beans to be
要使用的基础结构bean的数量
registered with the application context
在应用程序上下文中注册
this includes things like the task
这包括任务
execute the standard task executor
执行标准任务执行器
that's ring integration provides a
环的集成提供了
standard error channel that there's a
标准错误通道，有一个
pub sub channel that we have a logging
我们有记录的pub子频道
adapter subscribe to things like that
适配器订阅类似的东西
some basic infrastructure some some beam
一些基本的基础设施
post processes and various things that
发布流程和各种各样的东西
are required by the spring integration
Spring 集成所需
runtime to to do its work
运行时去做它的工作
so enable enable integration is the is
所以启用启用集成是
the mechanism that we use to to turn
我们用来转向的机制
that that feature on
该功能在
so dear so what is the DSL the the
亲爱的，那么DSL是什么
fundamental component of the DSL is an
DSL的基本组成部分是
integration flow of definition now in
现在的定义集成流程
order to create an integration flow
为了创建一个集成流程
definition we just create a beam
定义我们只是创建一个光束
integration flow I'll just call it flow
集成流程我将其称为流程
and we so we need to now build arab in
所以我们现在需要在
our flow definition it's sort of like a
我们的流程定义有点像
it's like a mega beam definition it's
就像是巨型光束的定义
actually a definition of an integration
实际上是整合的定义
flow channels endpoints and how they're
流动通道端点及其状况
wired together so as a beam we we just
连在一起，就像一条光束，我们只是
building that that flow definition when
在建立流程定义时
we actually instantiate the application
我们实际上实例化了应用程序
context literally when we refresh it the
从字面上看，当我们刷新它时
beam post processor finds that
光束后处理器发现
integration flow definition and will and
整合流程定义以及意愿和
will will basically go through that
基本上会经历
definition register all the endpoints
定义注册所有端点
wire them all together with the channel
将它们与通道连接在一起
with the appropriate channels so I'm
有适当的渠道，所以我
going to start off here using Java Java
将开始使用Java Java
8 lambdas because it's a little more
8个lambda，因为还多了一点
sexy and let's see where we go from here
性感，让我们看看我们从这里走到哪里
so I'm gonna I'm gonna return a flow and
所以我要返回一个流
which I'm defining as a lambda
我定义为lambda
expression I'm going to give it some
表达，我要给它一些
something to do so in this case I'm just
在这种情况下要做的只是
going to transform and we start off with
要转变，我们从开始
a spell expression to uppercase I'm just
大写字母的咒语表达
going to all I'm going to do is is is
我要做的就是
convert the string payload to an
将字符串有效负载转换为
uppercase version of it and then I'm
它的大写版本，然后我
going to actually send it now this will
现在要实际发送它
give you some idea of what I mean by we
让您了解我的意思
can handle anything that's that not
可以处理任何不是
doesn't have first-class support and in
没有一流的支持
this case I'm going to actually send it
这种情况下我要实际发送
to a a logging message handler so I'm
到一个日志消息处理程序，所以我
going to create a beam for that that log
将为该日志创建光束
have been
已经
and I'm just simply going to return a
我只是要返回一个
new logging and we're going to log it
新的日志记录，我们将对其进行记录
warn them okay so there we are with our
警告他们好吧，所以我们在那里
first DSL we have a flow that that
第一个DSL，我们有一个流程
starts with a channel and explain that
从一个频道开始，并解释说
in a minute and we transform the payload
一分钟后，我们将有效载荷转换
to uppercase and we can we could we can
大写，我们可以，我们可以
within just gonna route that message to
在短短的时间内就会将该消息路由到
a logger the first thing I want to do is
记录员，我要做的第一件事是
I'm going to auto wire in the channel
我要在通道中自动接线
and now one of the tricks because I use
现在是技巧之一，因为我使用
the lambda I need to put a qualifier on
我需要在预选赛上放一个lambda
here to tell the framework what what the
这里告诉框架什么
channel name is and the convention if
频道名称为，约定为
you're using a lambda star the flow is
您使用的是Lambda星，流是
the the channel gets a name of flow the
通道获得流的名称
flow name input so here we have our flow
流名称输入，所以在这里我们有流
using a lambda starts with a channel
使用Lambda始于通道
called flow input it's going to write it
称为流程输入，它将编写它
to transform to upcase it it's then
转换为大写字母
going to plug it so let us let us run
将其插入，让我们让我们运行
that
那
and does it always do this to me
而且它总是对我这样做
oh my
天啊
Herk well trust me like that message
赫克非常喜欢我这样的消息
just does go through I'm not sure what
只是确实经历了我不确定
what's happened to my configuration here
我的配置在这里发生了什么
is should be we should be getting one
应该是我们应该得到一个
log size at that point if I get time oh
如果我有时间的话，日志大小
well I'll go back and figure that out so
好吧，我回去想一想
let me let me just just just to prove
让我让我只是为了证明
that I'm I'm not I'm just going to do it
我是我不是我要去做
this out so what I've done here is I've
这样，所以我在这里所做的是
just said instead of a logging message
只是说而不是一条记录消息
handler I'm just going to I'm just going
经理，我要去，我要去，
to do it again
再做一次
hopefully Thank You Alton
希望谢谢你奥尔顿
I didn't actually write a test though
我实际上并没有写测试
okay yes indeed so and what I'm going to
好吧，是的，的确如此，我要去
do is just I'm going to say a new
只是我要说一个新的
messaging template for the channel in
中的频道的消息传递模板
and I'm going to send a message ID so it
我要发送一个消息ID
converts and there we go and there will
转换，那里我们去那里
write
写
okay
好的
one more time
再一次
Oh
哦
I need to tell them I need to tell that
我需要告诉他们我需要告诉
we're we're using spring of course and
当然，我们正在使用春季
this time finally we should we should
这次我们终于应该
get a message
得到消息
okay so we have we've sent a message to
好吧，我们已经发送了一条消息给
this channel this input channel a
此通道此输入通道a
floater input and transformed it w case
浮动输入并转换为w
and logged in apologize for the glitches
并为出现的故障道歉
there so now the thing is this can be
在那里，现在事情可以是
any spell expression so let me let me
任何咒语表达，让我让我
create a beam my transformer which is
创建一个光束，我的变压器是
just a POJO and I'm just going to return
只是一个POJO而我要返回
a new object and I'm just going to add a
一个新对象，我将添加一个
method public string transform
方法公共字符串转换
and I'm just going to return in plus
我将要返回加号
okay now I'm just going to concatenate
好吧，我现在要串联
it with itself and and so now this this
它本身，所以现在这个
spell expression is it's going to be
咒语表达将是
we're going to invoke this beam which is
我们将要调用的是
called my transformer this standard
我的变压器叫这个标准
spell my transformer what did I call it
拼写我的变压器我叫什么
transform payload
转换有效载荷
and again we have our output so we're
再次，我们有我们的输出，所以我们
now so now we've we've changed our spell
现在所以现在我们已经改变了我们的咒语
instead of instead of just using a
而不是仅仅使用一个
simple spell expression we can invoke a
简单的咒语表达，我们可以调用
POJO another thing we can do is is we
POJO我们可以做的另一件事是
can instead of using spell we can just
可以代替使用咒语，我们可以
use a lambda expression now in order to
现在使用lambda表达式以
give the compiler asan some help we have
给编译器提供一些帮助
to tell tell it what what we're
告诉我们我们在做什么
transforming from and to so now using a
现在和现在之间使用
lambda expression I can just say okay
lambda表情我可以说好
the I'm going to convert the payload I'm
我将要转换的有效载荷
just going to have a parameter P to
只是要有一个参数P
uppercase so now we have a lambda
大写，所以现在我们有一个lambda
version of exactly the same thing we've
完全相同的版本
avoided spell and where we're going to
避免咒语以及我们要去的地方
just just simply up case the up case the
只是只是大写的情况下
pelo
佩洛
all well and good this is this is a very
很好，很好，这是一个非常
nice succinct and but as I mentioned
很简洁，但是正如我提到的
before there are certain people that are
在某些人之前
not able to move to the job eight yet so
还不能搬到八号工作
let's see what this would look like with
让我们来看看
with Java sermon again everything I did
再次使用Java布道，我所做的一切
before with the spell expression that
之前的咒语表达是
can still be done with Java with Java 7
Java 7仍然可以通过Java完成
but we can't use this lambda to build
但我们不能使用此lambda进行构建
the flow with Java 7 so we have a we
Java 7的流程，所以我们有一个
have a factory called integration flows
有一个工厂称为整合流程
where we we actually say from and then
我们实际上从哪里说，然后
we give it some some channel name and
我们给它一些频道名称，
and this this integration flows a
这个整合流程
factory is is one of the core components
工厂是核心组成部分之一
as we'll see a bit later on for creating
我们稍后会看到
flows from things other than channels so
来自渠道以外的东西
if we want to start with the message
如果我们想从消息开始
source of polled message source etc we
轮询消息源等的来源
would use we would use this Factory but
将使用我们将使用此工厂，但
for now I'm just going to show basically
现在，我将主要展示
the same the same application without
相同的相同的应用程序，没有
using lambdas so I'll just comment the
使用lambdas，所以我只评论
lambda version out and there are a
lambda版本出来了，有一个
couple of things we can do one is to
我们可以做的几件事是
just use a an anonymous class which is
只需使用一个匿名类
which is just just like the lambda and
就像lambda和
we have a convenience convenience class
我们有一个便利班
a generic transform which allows us to
通用转换，使我们能够
to define a transformer
定义一个变压器
to overwrite them and
覆盖它们并
and we need and we just need to
我们需要，我们只需要
implement the method here public
在此处公开实施该方法
into uppercase so this is basically
变成大写，所以基本上
doing the same thing as what we did
做和我们做的一样的事情
before but we were using an anonymous
以前，但是我们使用匿名
class to do it this is functionally the
类来做到这一点在功能上
same as the as the lambda expression now
与现在的lambda表达式相同
when we're using the integration flows
当我们使用集成流程时
we don't have the benefit of the lambda
我们没有lambda的好处
so we have to use just the get method on
所以我们只需要使用get方法
the end which this basically is after
这基本上是在结束之后
we've finished building the flow we just
我们已经完成了流程的构建
get that beam and we read that back this
得到那束光，我们读回这个
get method rachet returns the
get方法rachet返回
integration flow class tickets that gets
获得的集成流程类凭单
returned to the the caller the gets
返回给调用者的获取
registered has been so this is this is
已注册，所以这是
basically exactly the same thing but
基本上完全一样，但是
using using Java 7 is that a Java 8 so
使用Java 7是Java 8
with that said the next thing I'm going
这样说，我接下来要去
to do is just just take a look through
要做的只是看一看
some of the test cases in in the in the
中的一些测试用例
framework so that we can see a little
框架，以便我们可以看到一点
bit more about about how the DSL works
有关DSL工作原理的更多信息
so I'm going to start with the this
所以我将从这个开始
integration flow tests which is the main
主要的集成流程测试
sort of main main test case for the for
的主要主要测试用例
the framework and one of the things I
框架和我要做的事情之一
want to I want to show is the some basic
我想展示的是一些基本的
capabilities so we have this this this
功能，所以我们有这个
simple context configuration one of the
简单上下文配置之一
one of the questions came up fairly
问题之一公平出现
frequently is well how do I do a control
经常好如何控制
bus programmatically means this enough
总线以编程方式意味着足够
in XML we're just angle brackets control
在XML中，我们只是尖括号控制
bus and we have a control bus it's very
巴士，我们有控制巴士，
simple with the with the DSL we just say
与DSL一样简单，我们只是说
we use integration flows which I just
我们使用整合流程
showed we say from a channel called
表明我们从一个名为
control bus we use the control bus build
控制总线我们使用控制总线构建
a method and then get it so we haven't
一种方法，然后得到它，所以我们没有
we now have a control bus that we can
现在我们有了控制总线
send messages to this channel to start
发送消息到该频道以开始
and stop
停下来
adapters or do anything that you
适配器或您所做的任何事情
anything that you wish to the biocontrol
您想要进行生物防治的任何东西
bus this this particular test shows how
这个特殊的测试显示了如何
to how to create the default polar the
如何创建默认极坐标
default polar is in XML if you recall
如果您记得的话，默认Polar是XML
that said this is usually a table that
说这通常是一张桌子
is a top-level item where it's a top
是顶级商品，它是顶级商品
level polar where the the beam is
光束所在的水平极
designated has been the default polar
指定为默认极性
this polar will be used for any polling
此极将用于任何轮询
requirements such as polled message
要求，例如轮询消息
sources or polled channels when no
没有时的来源或轮询渠道
specific polar has been provided so this
提供了特定的极性，因此
this been here is basically saying this
这个来这里基本上是在说这个
is my default polar which runs at this
这是我的默认极点
this fixed rate and has you know one
这个固定汇率，你知道吗
next message purport the the next beam
下一条消息表示下一条光束
in this test is that she shows you how
在这次测试中，她向您展示了
to override the default task scheduler I
覆盖默认任务计划程序I
mentioned that the the enable
提到启用
integration annotation it turns out of a
集成批注的结果是
whole bunch of infrastructure beans or
整堆基础架构bean或
defines a whole bunch of infrastructure
定义了一堆基础架构
beans well one of those beans is the is
bean 好那些 bean 之一是
a task scheduler and by default it has
一个任务计划程序，默认情况下它具有
10 threads so if you need to override
10个线程，因此如果您需要覆盖
that then you can simply add this bean
那你可以简单地添加这个bean
to your context with the with the
与您的环境
appropriate name and it will override
适当的名称，它将覆盖
the default task scheduler
默认任务计划程序
scrolling down some more we can actually
向下滚动一些，我们实际上可以
start looking at looking at some flows
开始看着一些流量
now so and in this case we're going to
现在，在这种情况下，我们将
look at the filter so the filter method
看一下过滤器，所以过滤方法
on the integration flow definition gives
关于集成流程的定义给出了
us the ability to filter messages as
我们能够将邮件过滤为
with as with all filters and swing
与所有过滤器和秋千一样
integration so and what we see here with
整合以及我们在这里看到的
the definition is is the actual filter
定义是实际的过滤器
lambda which is basically the same where
lambda基本上是一样的
we're going to filter on payloads that
我们将对有效载荷进行过滤
are strings and then the second argument
是字符串，然后是第二个参数
to the filter method is the endpoint
过滤方法是终点
definition spec in this case we've done
在这种情况下，我们已经定义了规范
an ID filter and then typically with
ID过滤器，然后通常使用
filters we just send a message to a
过滤器，我们只是向
discard Channel and then if we would do
放弃频道，然后如果我们愿意
an XML configuration we would have to
XML配置，我们将不得不
have another flow that that consumes
有另一个消耗的流量
from that filter channel and/or that
从那个过滤器通道和/或那个
discard channel and then take some
放弃渠道，然后采取一些
action on the discarded messages in this
在此对丢弃的消息采取的措施
case we're actually demonstrating a
情况下，我们实际上正在展示
fairly nice capability of the the DSL in
DSL的相当不错的功能
that we can actually have sub flows
我们实际上可以有子流
within the flow so this is our
在流中，所以这是我们的
integration flow called flow to but the
集成流称为流向，但
discard typically discard you might just
丢弃通常会丢弃，您可能只是
want to log something or maybe send it
想要记录或发送
to a rabbit queue ordered something
到兔子队列点东西
basic with messages that are discarded
基本的消息被丢弃
so rather than have to write a whole new
所以不必写一个全新的
flow that hangs off the discard channel
悬挂丢弃通道的流量
we have this discard flow method which
我们有这种丢弃流方法
enables us to actually write another
使我们能够实际编写另一个
flow it's a sub flow off the main flow
流是主流的子流
and if we actually go look at this this
如果我们真的去看看这个
definition you will see that the
定义，您将看到
argument is another integration flow
论点是另一种整合流程
again we're using a lambda so the
再次，我们使用lambda，所以
discard flow and it can have anything on
丢弃流，它可以有任何东西
it in this case all we're doing is
在这种情况下，我们要做的就是
transforming the discarded message we're
转换我们丢弃的消息
adding some text to it and then sending
向其中添加一些文本，然后发送
it and then we're still sending it to a
它，然后我们仍将其发送到
channel which mean in this case you know
频道，在这种情况下，您知道
you would still be doing something to it
你仍然会对此有所作为
but but you could easily dispose of it
但您可以轻松处置它
completely within this discard flow
完全在此丢弃流程之内
after the filter so and so messages that
在过滤器等消息之后
are passed and messages that don't pass
已通过，未通过的消息
the filter get get right to this this
过滤器得到正确的这个
sub flow messages the pastor filter ie
子流消息牧师过滤器即
those that are strings will now drop
那些是字符串的现在将下降
down to the the remainder of the flow
向下流到其余部分
definition in this case we were
在这种情况下，我们的定义是
specifically saying that we're naming
特别是说我们在命名
the channel so we can do things like
渠道，这样我们就可以做
like add global interceptors so that we
例如添加全局拦截器，以便我们
could intercept this message if
如果可以拦截此消息
necessary
必要
or we could omit that and the framework
或者我们可以忽略这一点和框架
will just use an internal channel to it
只会使用内部频道
to wire them together the fixed
将它们固定在一起
subscriber channel is a special use case
用户频道是一种特殊的用例
that is you
那是你
is to tightly bind endpoints together
是将端点紧密绑定在一起
for for efficiency if needed and then
为了提高效率（如果需要），然后
we're doing it within another transform
我们正在另一个转换中进行
we were so we will and again we give in
我们曾经如此，所以我们将一再屈服
the compiler hints that we converted for
编译器提示我们转换为
a string to an integer and we're simply
一个字符串到一个整数，我们就是
using a function the reference here the
使用功能参考这里
passing method on the integer class we
在整数类上传递方法我们
have another payer when you have another
当您有另一个付款人时
transformer this this demonstrates the
变压器这证明了
fact that we can we can add any
我们可以添加的事实
transformer object we can just read
我们可以阅读的变压器对象
declare one in line here and in this
在此和此声明一个
case we're actually configuring the
如果我们实际上是在配置
endpoint itself such as the the author's
端点本身，例如作者的
data those those attributes that are on
记录那些属性
the on the endpoint rather than the
在端点而不是
transformer another transformer and so
变压器另一个变压器等等
this flows basically the filter and then
这基本上使过滤器流动，然后
a few a few transformers the next the
几个变形金刚下
next flow I'd like to show you is this
我想向您展示的下一个流程是
publish/subscribe channel flow in that
在其中发布/订阅频道流
typically in the XML world if you want
如果需要，通常在XML世界中
to send a message to multiple
向多个人发送消息
destinations you can use a recipient
您可以使用收件人的目的地
list router or you can use a
列出路由器，或者您可以使用
publish/subscribe channel
发布/订阅频道
in in this case it also shows again how
在这种情况下，它也再次显示了
we can subscribe sub flows to a publish
我们可以将子流订阅到发布
subscribe channel so let's consider a
订阅频道，让我们考虑
fairly typical scenario where we're
相当典型的场景
sending a message to an outbound channel
向出站通道发送消息
adapter by definition there's no result
适配器根据定义没有结果
from that what if you want to send a
从那如果你想发送一个
result to your caller that let's say a
结果给您的来电者，让我们说一个
send mail was successful by default when
默认情况下，发送邮件成功
you sent well the way a send mail
您发送邮件的方式发送得很好
adapter works is you send the message in
适配器正常工作是您在发送消息
its and it's gone it's sent so fairly
它的它已经消失了，它发送得很公平
common pattern is to subscribe a second
常见的模式是订阅第二个
endpoint to that publish/subscribe
该发布/订阅的端点
channel that would be invoked once the
一旦
mail was sent successfully and then we
邮件已成功发送，然后我们
would return the return sum result to
将返回的总和结果返回到
the caller from that second subscriber
第二个订户的呼叫者
to the publish/subscribe channel and you
到发布/订阅频道，您
can do that in the end with the dsl as
最后可以用dsl作为
well but again we have this can be
好吧，不过我们有这个可以
where we can we can add a sub flow we
我们可以在哪里添加子流
can subscribe a sub flow to a
可以将子流订阅到
publish/subscribe channel so in this
发布/订阅频道，因此在此
particular instance this this particular
这个特殊的实例
instance has a as a it's using an
实例具有一个，它正在使用
executor on the pub sub channel so these
pub子通道上的执行程序，所以这些
these subscribers will be invoked in
这些订户将在中被调用
parallel assuming the yes this is using
并行，假设使用的是
the cash thread port so these sub flows
现金线程端口，以便这些子流
will be invoked in parallel on different
将在不同的位置并行调用
threads and then third subscriber is the
线程，然后第三个订阅者是
main flow itself so it's just another
主流本身，所以它只是另一个
flavor when you're using pub sub Cannell
使用pub sub Cannell时的风味
you can use them as you always have and
您可以像往常一样使用它们，并且
just attach different flows to those
只是将不同的流程附加到那些
channels that have defined us where or
定义我们在哪里的渠道或
you can define them as sub flows within
您可以将它们定义为内部的子流
the within the definition itself and
定义本身中的
okay now I mentioned I mentioned that
好吧，现在我提到我提到了
that we have some first-class support
我们有一些一流的支持
and we have some sort some adapters that
我们有一些适配器
don't have first-class support as I
我没有一流的支持
mentioned we we can always invoke any
提到我们可以随时调用任何
message handler through the handle
通过句柄的消息处理程序
method let's just take a quick look at
方法让我们快速浏览一下
one of the one of the the tests that
其中一项测试
does have one of the modules that does
确实有其中一个模块
have first-class support and that that's
有一流的支持，那就是
mail so with the mail we have we
邮件，所以我们有邮件
basically have these factory methods
基本上有这些工厂方法
that will create adapters for us and and
这将为我们和
also other things such as like here we
还有其他事情，例如这里
have this as mail this mail factory
有这个作为邮件工厂
class that has a number of static
具有多个静态值的类
methods on in this case headers that
在这种情况下，标头上的方法
enables us to build ahead as headers
使我们能够作为头文件向前发展
builder that we can set sadist to but
我们可以设置虐待狂的建设者，但是
the that the point
那一点
trying to make about handle so let's say
试图处理一下，所以说
we want to we want to handle some
我们想要处理一些
something like mqtt adapter which we
像mqtt适配器这样的东西
don't have first card we don't have a
没有第一张卡，我们没有
factory a method to create an MQTT
工厂创建MQTT的方法
adapter so let's let's see how we would
适配器，让我们看看如何
do that one thing we could do is I'm
做那件事我们可以做的就是我
just going to create a MQTT beam public
只是要创建一个MQTT梁公共
MQTT part message handle I'm just going
我要去的MQTT零件消息句柄
to call MQTT and and we can return a new
调用MQTT，我们可以返回一个新的
message handler with with whatever we
消息处理程序，无论我们做什么
configure it so so anything that
配置它，以便任何东西
although we said we don't have
虽然我们说我们没有
first-class support you can easily wire
一流的支持，您可以轻松接线
up the beam for those adapters that that
那些适配器的光束
we don't have first-class support for
我们没有一流的支持
and invoke them via the handle method in
并通过中的handle方法调用它们
the case of mail so we can actually say
邮件的情况，所以我们可以说
we can use the factory method male I
我们可以用工厂法男
have an adapter and then we can give it
有一个适配器，然后我们可以给它
a host so the difference is with
一个主机，所以区别在于
first-class support you get you get this
一流的支持，您能得到这个
builder this fluent Builder API to build
构建此流利的Builder API进行构建
the the endpoint or the message handler
端点或消息处理程序
in this case with with those modules
在这种情况下与那些模块
that we don't yet have first-class for
我们还没有一流的
support you would just create the beam
支持你就可以创造光束
as a regular at beam definition and then
作为常规的光束定义，然后
provide a reference to it in the handle
在句柄中为其提供参考
method another question that came up is
方法出现的另一个问题是
well what if I just have some kind of
好吧，如果我只有某种
POJO I'm just gonna call it an object
POJO我只是称它为对象
and I've got I've got some some object
我有一些东西
or some class that I have a I have some
或我有一些课程我有一些
some podium method on it
一些讲台上的方法
and I'm going to expose a message
我将公开一条消息
and we have a flavor of the of the
而且我们有
handle method on the deer cell that
鹿细胞的处理方法
enables us now to invoke that poacher so
现在使我们能够调用该偷猎者
we just give it the the beam name and
我们给它起梁的名称，
then the method name that we want to
然后我们想要的方法名称
invoke and so just like with a with the
调用，就像用
XML configuration where we can have the
XML配置，我们可以
service activators and such that are
服务激活器等
simple polo poachers then then we have
简单的马球偷猎者，那么我们有
that same capability through the through
通过相同的能力
the handle method
处理方法
okay so again that's that's for cases
好吧，那又是针对情况
where we don't have you know for things
我们不知道你在哪里
like Paro where we want to show and or
就像我们想展示的Paro一样，或
we can we can invite inject any any
我们可以邀请任何人加入
message handler in fact you know this is
消息处理程序实际上您知道这是
a POJO you could also implement your own
POJO，您也可以实现自己的POJO
message handler this doesn't have to be
消息处理程序，这不一定是
part of the message handler interfaces
消息处理程序接口的一部分
all we need to return and we can inject
我们需要返回，我们可以注入
that into any handle method let's see
进入任何handle方法
so AMQP so so a rabbit support again we
所以AMQP所以兔子再次支持我们
have webson first-class support for
拥有webson的一流支持
rabbit we have this this if i go to do
兔子，如果我去的话，我们有这个
that actually go to the just look at the
实际去看看
AMQP factory so again a number of number
AMQP工厂如此再次数
of factory methods on the same QP
在同一QP上的工厂方法
factory and in bang gateway and just the
工厂和爆炸网关，只是
internal as you can see a little bit
您可以看到内部
about what what you get is is we have
关于你得到的是我们有
these specification classes and these
这些规范类以及这些
like invalid gateway spec is our builder
像无效的网关规范是我们的构建者
our fluent api for building a for
我们的流利的api用于构建
building an n QP gateway so if we look
建立一个n QP网关，所以如果我们看
at the the tests test configuration so
在测试测试配置中
we were just using this factory method
我们只是使用这种工厂方法
on the factory class AMQP the in Bangka
在班加的AMQP工厂级
a we give it
一个我们给它
it referenced the connection factory and
它引用了连接工厂，
the queue that it's going to listen on
将要监听的队列
and of course just transforming and then
当然，只是转变，然后
transform it so it's a witness this
改变它，所以它是一个见证
particular test is going to send back
特定测试将退回
hello concatenate it on to the input and
你好，将其连接到输入并
then upper cases then similarly on the
然后大写然后类似地在
outbound flow we're going to start with
我们将从这里开始
a within this case we're using a name QP
在这种情况下，我们使用名称QP
back channel which is another factory
后通道是另一个工厂
method on the NQ p factory and as those
NQ p工厂的方法以及那些
you're aware of JMS named QP have
您知道名为QP的JMS具有
persistent channel so so if you have a
持续性频道，所以如果您有一个
chip mid flow channel that you need to
您需要的芯片中流通道
unique persistence on then then you can
这样就可以保持独特的持久性
use a rabbit or JMS to persist that so
用兔子或JMS来坚持
in this particular case the start of
在这种情况下，
this flow is is downstream of a name QP
该流是名称QP的下游
back to channel quarter call called n QP
返回频道季度通话，称为n QP
input and then again we're passing it to
输入，然后再次将其传递给
handler and then again this Factory is
处理程序，然后这个工厂再次
our band adapter factory method is going
我们的频段适配器工厂方法正在发展
to build us using a fluent API is going
使用流利的API来建立我们
to build the build the band after for us
为我们建立乐队
and send the message
并发送消息
and similarly we this shows another
同样，我们显示了另一个
flavor of the from the earlier from we
来自我们早期的风味
did was start from a from a channel
是从渠道开始的
adapter in this case we're starting from
在这种情况下，我们从
a message producer so this is like a a
消息产生者，所以这就像一个
message driven inbound channel adapter
消息驱动的入站通道适配器
that's going to going to create messages
这将要创建消息
and send them to this this transformer
并将它们发送到此变压器
so I would recommend if the this tests
所以我建议如果这个测试
are a good place to start the the
是开始的好地方
resources that we've we've already
我们已经拥有的资源
discussed the the previous webinars the
讨论了以前的网络研讨会
the two tutorials that autumn did the
那个秋天的两个教程
these test cases are great examples and
这些测试案例是很好的例子，
of course the reference guide itself
当然参考指南本身
will give you good a good feel of how
会给你很好的感觉
how to build an application using the
如何使用
DSL
DSL
I just like to I guess finish with
我只想结束
saying that or at least finish the
说或至少完成
speaking part before we go to Q&amp;A how to
在我们去问答环节之前，
how to reach us anything they like
如何找到我们喜欢的任何东西
anyway we're looking for feedback on the
无论如何，我们正在寻找有关
you know what do you need next in terms
你知道接下来你需要什么
of the first class support we have these
一流的支持，我们有这些
already we need to know we need
已经我们需要知道我们需要
something some sort of sequencing that
一些排序的东西
when to do the the remaining adapters
什么时候做其余的适配器
you can reach us on stack overflow with
您可以通过以下方式与我们联系
the spring integration tag and of course
Spring 集成标签，当然
the JIRA is that there for any any new
JIRA有任何新东西
features suggested that you guys have
功能建议你们有
with that I'll turn it over to Peter for
这样我就交给彼得
to handle the Q&amp;A excellent hey Gary
负责问答环节，嘿，加里
the next question comes from Marco and
下一个问题来自Marco和
he was curious what kind of support is
他很好奇是什么样的支持
provided for LDAP and just you know LDAP
提供给LDAP，而您知道LDAP
servers in general on I you know usually
我一般都知道服务器
you know my experience usually when
你通常知道我的经历
people ask about LDAP they're more
人们问有关LDAP的更多信息
curious about it as an authentication
对其进行身份验证感到好奇
store right on so I would kind of you
储存在正确的位置，这样我会很喜欢你
know Marco if you can hear me I would I
知道马可，如果你能听见我，我会
would take a look at the spring LDAP
来看看 Spring 的LDAP
project if that's your angle but if
项目，如果那是你的角度，但如果
you're really thinking about actually
你真的在想
connecting to it as a spring integration
作为Spring 集成连接到它
you know directly from spring
你直接从 Spring 知道
integration because you need the data on
集成，因为您需要数据
in there um actually everything spring
那里实际上是 Spring
out that does do a decent job with that
这样做确实做得不错
as well but Stumm I don't know Gary is
也是，但Stumm我不知道Gary是
that something you guys have a channel
你们有一个频道
adapter for I wouldn't imagine you would
我无法想象的适配器
right wait no we don't right now I mean
好的，等待，不，我们现在不
it has actually come up before where you
它实际上已经出现在您的位置之前
might me know maybe during a flow you
我可以知道吗？
might want to do some kind and all that
可能想做某种事情
lookup and again I it hasn't really
查找，然后我又没有
reached the the barrier or the threshold
达到障碍或门槛
of oh wow we really need to write a
哦，我们真的需要写一个
specific adapter to do that but as
特定的适配器来做到这一点，但作为
penis's spring LDAP is a is a great
阴茎的 Spring LDAP是一个伟大的
abstraction on top of the ARP API so you
ARP API之上的抽象，因此您
don't need to get down into the weeds
不需要深入杂草
and yeah it would be very easy to to
是的，这很容易
write your own POJO that invokes the
编写自己的POJO来调用
spring LDAP and then you you invoke that
Spring 的LDAP，然后您调用
POJO from a spring integration service
来自Spring 集成服务的POJO
and service activator so in in the in
和服务激活器，所以在
the context of a DSL you would just use
您将使用的DSL上下文
that that handle method to to answer so
这样处理方法来回答
let me let me just go back to okay
让我让我回去好吗
because what what what ever what I
因为无论我怎样
remember about the spring LDAP is that
记得 Spring 的LDAP是
it actually has some facility it's not
它实际上有一些设施，不是
just about the authentication that it
关于它的身份验证
has some facility for actually kind of
有一些设施，实际上是
traversing and right right right so
遍历和对对对
usually when data the actual data and
通常在实际数据和
all that so that could be you know well
所有这一切可能就是你很清楚
right yeah you to turn into a Nadella
是的，你变成纳德拉了
agression adapter actually right right
攻击适配器实际上是对的
but but yes so you can do things like
但是是的，所以你可以做类似的事情
you you can query LDAP you can query the
您可以查询LDAP您可以查询
directory tree you can
您可以的目录树
search for search for objects in in LDAP
在LDAP中搜索对象
and you do that via spring LDAP and you
然后通过spring LDAP进行操作
would just simply do that by you know my
只是因为你知道我会这样做
you know you could just write a POJO
你知道你可以写一个POJO
that wraps the wraps that spring LDAP
包裹了LDAP的 Spring
code and and then you can do you can
代码，然后您就可以做到
based on a message your based on
根据您基于的消息
properties of the message you can do
您可以执行的邮件属性
those those lookups and searches so and
那些查找和搜索等等
that's really true of any technology I
我使用的任何技术都是如此
mean sometimes people have asked this
意味着有时候人们问了这个
well you know that the JDBC doctors
好吧，您知道JDBC医生
don't do exactly what I want to do and
不完全按照我的意愿去做
in terms of the outbound adapters well
就出站适配器而言
in that case just write your own write
在那种情况下，只写自己的写
your own wrapper around the JDBC
您自己的JDBC包装器
template to do exactly what you want to
模板完全可以执行您想要的操作
do and then invoke that poggio either
做然后调用那个钢琴
from as a service activator from from an
来自作为一个服务激活者
annotation or an external perspective or
注释或外部视角或
via one acquire this handle method in
通过一个获取这种处理方法
the in the DSL wear handle method takes
DSL磨损处理方法中的
any message handler so you can you can
任何消息处理程序，以便您可以
do pretty much anything you want within
做你想做的几乎所有事情
the spring integration flow by just
Spring 整合流程
writing a little bit of glue code
写一点胶水代码
between the the integration API and the
在集成API和
component that you want to interact with
您要与之交互的组件
whether that be some special capability
是否有某种特殊能力
of the JDBC template that we don't cover
我们不介绍的JDBC模板
or something like spring elder
或像 Spring 长者
yep excellent cool thanks for that Gary
是的，非常酷，谢谢你的加里
yeah so let's the next question is from
是的，让我们接下来的问题是
Mickey weak wick with two eyes that cool
米奇柔软的灯芯，两只眼睛凉爽
um his question is uh what do I do in
嗯，他的问题是呃，我该怎么办
case I want to use a non first class
我想使用非头等舱的情况
component right so I think I think I
组件正确，所以我想我想我
covered that so like like is my screen
覆盖，就像我的屏幕一样
still shed yeah it is as though yeah and
仍然脱落是的，好像是的，
search is fine so in this case so MQTT
搜索很好，因此在这种情况下，MQTT
we don't we don't have closed class
我们不，我们没有封闭式课程
support for mqtt right so I actually
支持mqtt对，所以我实际上
want to I want to receive data from an
我想从
MQTT adapter well I don't have I can't
MQTT适配器很好，我没有，我不能
say you know if we had first-class
说你知道我们是否有一流的
support then we'd have something like
支持，那么我们会喜欢
this MQTT dot inbound and then you know
此MQTT点入站，然后您知道
some some configuration for for that so
为此一些配置
we would actually have a DSL a fluent
我们实际上可以流畅地使用DSL
API for building and mqtt adapter well
用于构建和mqtt适配器的API
we don't we don't have that today we
我们不，我们今天没有
don't have it yet so so the way the way
还没有，所以方式
we do that is we just we just create
我们这样做就是我们只是创建
arum qtt adapter here so so we could
阿鲁姆QTT适配器在这里，所以我们可以
simply just just build our build our
只是只是建立我们的建立我们的
adapter here now we need some we need
适配器在这里，我们需要一些我们需要的
some properties for that if I remember
我记得有一些特性
correctly
正确地
like we need you know we need a URL when
就像我们需要您知道我们需要一个URL
you client IDs and stuff like that so we
您的客户ID之类的东西，所以我们
will just build the we just build the
将只建立我们只建立
adapter this is the URL and the client
适配器，这是URL和客户端
ID etc so we just build and now whatever
ID等，因此我们只需构建即可
else we need to do to configure it and
否则我们需要做配置
then we would just return the adapter so
那么我们将只返回适配器
we know we don't have first-class
我们知道我们没有一流的
support in terms of a builder API for an
在构建器API方面的支持
mqtt adapter it's very easy to just
mqtt适配器，非常容易
invoke this message handler directly
直接调用此消息处理程序
from the from the flow so in this case
从流所以在这种情况下
we're actually receiving band I say we
我们实际上是在接收乐队，我说我们
want to do something let's say we want
想做某事，假设我们要
to receive from mqtt and then transform
从mqtt接收，然后进行转换
it whatever whatever the transform is
无论转换是什么
and then we want to send it to some
然后我们要发送给一些
other mqt let me just come in access we
其他mqt让我只要进入我们
just if we then want to send it to
就算我们要发送给
another to an outbound MQTT adapter then
另一个到出站MQTT适配器，然后
we would just build a we can even do it
我们将建立一个我们甚至可以做到的
in here mq TC I have a message handler
在这里mq TC我有一个消息处理程序
you know just just just build the build
你知道只是建立
the adapter right there in the in the
适配器就在其中
job
工作
so I don't want to I don't want to over
所以我不想我不想结束
emphasize I mean it's it's the
强调我的意思是
first-class support is really what we're
一流的支持才是我们真正的目标
talking about is actually having that
谈论的实际上是
fluid that fluent API for building these
流畅的API用于构建这些
components you can always build any
您可以随时构建的组件
component using traditional Java
使用传统Java的组件
configuration awesome Gary thank you so
很棒的配置Gary如此谢谢
much umm okay so let's see I think I
好吧，让我看看我
think we just got last one last question
认为我们只是最后一个问题
from Eric Rodriguez oh and by the way
来自埃里克·罗德里格斯（Eric Rodriguez）
folks um you know if you do have
乡亲，你知道你是否有
questions now is the time so please
现在是时候提问了，所以请
don't be shy
不要害羞
um Eric asks he's not sure if this is
嗯，埃里克（Eric）问他不确定这是否是
really a valid use case but are there
确实是一个有效的用例，但是在那里
any other spring
其他任何 Spring
that can be used in combination with
可以与
spring integration to provide a CQRS
Spring 集成以提供CQRS
event sourcing something like axon
事件采购像轴突
framework I'm not particular I'm not
框架我不是特别的我不是
familiar with that that particular
熟悉那个细节
framework myself but but yeah I mean I
构架自己，但是的，我是说我
pretty much anything any any integration
几乎任何集成
is capable you know you can very easily
有能力知道你可以很容易地
integrate it into into the integration
整合到整合中
framework one thing I did want to
框架我想做的一件事
mention which which I failed to and was
提到我未能做到的
the spring integration is used
使用Spring 集成
extensively within within spring XD and
在XD春季之内
spring XD go back to
Spring XD回到
excuse me so by the way Gary I've hurt
对不起，所以我加里受伤了
seen this acronym but hadn't hurt I
看过这个缩写词，但没有伤害我
didn't know exactly what it meant
不知道到底是什么意思
apparently CQRS stands for a common
显然，CQRS代表一个共同点
command queer excuse me command and
命令酷儿请问命令和
query responsibility segregation I don't
查询责任隔离我不
know if that helps but yeah this is
知道是否有帮助，但是是的
something we have sort of an out of the
我们有点
box you know channel adapts before but
您知道频道之前适应过的方框
yes you're saying you know as we as we
是的，你是说你知道我们一样
just saw right it's very easy to do so
刚看对就很容易做到
what's the typical the typical
典型的是什么
progression of these things is if there
这些事情的进展是否存在
is a if there's if there's tremendous
如果有的话
demand for it then then we typically
需求然后我们通常
will put it right into the core
将其正确地放入核心
framework now we get lots of requests
框架，现在我们收到了很多请求
for the same thing like mqtt that came
对于像mqtt一样的东西
up fairly yeah fairly common and then
相当普遍，然后
but a bit so we start off with
但是有一点，所以我们从
extensions and people people can
扩展和人们可以
contribute extensions and then
贡献扩展，然后
eventually they get promoted into the
最终他们被提升为
core project I just just want to touch
我只想触摸的核心项目
on this as well and they did the spring
在这方面，他们做了 Spring
XD one one is coming out real soon and
XD一个即将面世，
one of the things that they've done in
他们所做的其中一件事情
in one one is the support of the Java
一是Java的支持
DSL the Java DSL modules so in this
DSL Java Java DSL模块在此
particular case it's a simple it's a
特殊情况很简单
simple transformer module but but they
简单的变压器模块，但是它们
you can now build no XML you can build a
您现在无法构建XML，而您可以构建
spring XD modules directly with the DSL
直接通过DSL弹出XD模块
and just just to look at that example if
只是看那个例子，如果
you go to spring XD samples you'll see
你去春季XD样品，你会看到
that down on Durham
落在达勒姆身上
under this SIDS our module and actually
在这个小岛屿发展中国家的模块下
I think this is a great this is a missus
我认为这太好了，这是小姐
kid that you bring this example up carry
你把这个例子提起来的孩子
because you know Eric's question being
因为你知道埃里克的问题是
about a kind of event sourcing I'm not
关于一种事件源，我不是
from listed backs on framework either
从框架上列出的支持
but just because he says event sourcing
只是因为他说事件来源
to me that that you know it sounds like
对我来说，你知道这听起来像
sounds like something maybe kind of a
听起来可能有点像
sink or you know streaming or something
下沉或您知道流媒体或其他内容
like that and Exedy is spring XD kind of
这样，Exedy是Spring XD的一种
it represents a sort of rapid
它代表了一种快速
application development even above and
甚至以上的应用程序开发
on top of spring integration and is
在 Spring Integration 的基础上，
specifically in many cases built for
特别是在很多情况下
dealing with stream processing and you
处理流处理，您
know dealing with high throughput events
知道处理高吞吐量事件
so even though there isn't you know
所以即使你不知道
there isn't a bolt on you know because
没有螺栓，因为
his question was hey I'm not sure this
他的问题是嘿，我不确定
is a valid use case right and I'm
是有效的用例权利，我是
thinking maybe he means maybe I
想着也许他意味着我
shouldn't bolt on some sort of event you
不应该在某种事情上发生
know high-speed event framework to
知道高速事件框架
spring integration you know that MAME
Spring 整合，你知道MAME
that may or may not be a valid use case
可能是无效的用例
but spring XD is clearly meant to do
但是Spring XD显然是可以做到的
that
那
and you know is built directly on spring
而且您知道直接建立在Spring 上
integration right so I think it is a
集成权，所以我认为这是一个
valid use case and I think jxt provides
有效的用例，我认为jxt提供了
that extra bit of value for for hooking
挂钩的额外价值
into streams or poking into sort of
进入溪流或戳入
high-throughput async type frameworks
高吞吐量异步类型框架
I'm going to take a quick look at axon
我将快速浏览轴突
framework Walter while we're talking
我们正在谈论框架Walter
this through because I'm just kind of
因为我只是一种
curious now just one other point about
现在很好奇
XD while we're on the subject for those
XD，而我们正在针对这些主题
that haven't looked at it yet I mean it
还没有看过它，我是说真的
does build on spring integration but it
确实基于spring集成，但它
does bring some some significant value
确实带来了一些重大价值
adds even for for you know non data
即使您知道非数据也可以添加
intensive applications that use spring
使用spring的密集型应用程序
integration for example spring spring XD
集成，例如spring spring XD
has the capability of a failover and and
具有故障转移的能力，并且
it manages instances of your spring
它管理着你的 Spring 的实例
integration flows so for example let's
整合流程，例如
say we have a an FTP adapter that is
说我们有一个FTP适配器
polling a shared resource like a NFS
轮询共享资源（例如NFS）
share or something then and then one of
共享或某些东西，然后其中之一
the classic example one of the classic
经典的例子之一
problems is how do I make that resilient
问题是我如何使自己具有韧性
so if I lose my server you know I've
因此，如果我丢失服务器，就知道我已经
lost my capability yet but on the other
失去了我的能力，但另一方面
hand you don't want you don't want two
手你不想要你不想要两个
instances running because they both get
实例正在运行，因为它们都可以
the same file unless you do some kind of
相同的文件，除非您执行某种操作
a global locking strategy with which is
全局锁定策略
cable which is available now in spring
电缆现已在春季上市
integration but but typically you might
集成，但通常您可能
want to consider having a using spring
想考虑使用Spring
XD to host your X in integration
XD托管您的X集成
application because then the XD admin if
应用程序，因为如果XD管理员
it detects that the FTP adapter goes
它检测到FTP适配器
down it it can then fire up another
向下它可以然后发射另一个
instance for you so so that's this
实例，所以就是这样
definitely something to look at for
绝对是要寻找的东西
resiliency and failover and etc as well
弹性和故障转移等
as dynamic scaling of course the X
作为X的动态缩放
Deacon can you can add add more
执事可以添加吗
containers if your workload goes up so
容器，如果您的工作量增加
Gary I just did a quick little peek
加里，我只是快速浏览了一下
because I was curious it looks like axon
因为我很好奇它看起来像轴突
is a form of async it looks like it's
是一种异步形式，看起来像是
kind of like a you know reification for
有点像你知道的具体化
a particular design pattern for
一种特定的设计模式
asynchronous process processing so on
异步处理等
and anyway just point of interest um on
而且无论如何只是兴趣点
so let's see leonardo silva asks if
让我们看看莱昂纳多·席尔瓦（Leonardo Silva）问
there's any way to monitor these flows
有任何方法可以监控这些流量
artemis ponded you know hey do you mean
阿耳emi弥斯深思你知道你的意思
like Jay Max and he said well you know
像杰伊·麦克斯（Jay Max），他说很好，你知道
maybe um but you know he's looking for a
也许嗯，但你知道他在找一个
place where he can see his runtime flows
他可以看到其运行时流的地方
response times status that crisis so if
响应时间是危机的状态，所以如果
you if you enable a jmx and in I don't
你，如果你启用一个JMX，我不
remember what the annotation is for when
记住什么时候注释是什么
using XML but but if you enable jmx
使用XML，但是如果启用jmx
then then all of the integration
然后所有的整合
components will maintain stats so every
组件将保持统计信息，因此每个
channel so you can see send rates you
频道，以便您可以查看发送价格
can see q q depth you can see all kinds
可以看到QQ深度，可以看到各种
of statistics about messages through the
通过
system so so JM x is the phys the first
系统，因此JM x是第一个phys
place to look for sure just adjust we
确定要调整的地方
just enable J max yep
只需启用J max是
excellent um and then actually I want to
优秀的嗯，然后我实际上想
go back to that question from Eric for
回到Eric的问题
just a second real quick and just
只是第二个真正的快速而公正
mention that we were talking about you
提到我们在谈论你
know plugging something like an event
知道插入诸如事件之类的东西
generation stream you know like an axon
就像轴突一样，你知道的一代流
or you know let's say it was like rx
或者你知道我们说它像RX
Java or you know something like that or
Java或您知道类似的东西或
a reactor maybe you know but but reactor
反应堆也许你知道，但是反应堆
we actually already do have a sources
我们实际上已经有一个资源
and sinks for from at the at the spring
从 Spring 开始
XD level I can't quite remember whether
XD级我不太记得
we're doing that as a spring integration
我们将其作为 Spring Integration
level as well or not but you know the
水平与否，但你知道
the if you're if you're looking to
如果您正在寻找
extend spring integration extending
延伸Spring 整合延伸
spring integration is entirely built on
Spring 集成完全建立在
the same experience as building spring
与建造Spring 一样的经验
integration channel adapters so you know
集成通道适配器，所以您知道
how to do that you know how to extend
该怎么做，你知道如何扩展
modules for spring XD it's it is a good
Spring XD的模块，这是一个很好的选择
same thing because XT is literally built
一样是因为XT实际上是构建的
directly on top of right and and and
直接在权利和和
actually you know new channel adaptors
实际上您知道新的通道适配器
are really easy I mean they you just
真的很容易，我是说他们你
implement or you extend a classical
实施或扩展经典
message producer support and that back
消息生产者的支持和支持
classes then gives you the ability to
然后，课程使您能够
emit messages into the into the
向发出消息
framework we are looking at more and
我们正在研究的框架以及
more integration with project reactants
与项目反应物的更多整合
and spring integration as you mentioned
您提到的Spring 整合
there's some work going on in X D we
我们在XD中正在进行一些工作
also have in in spring integration 4.1
在Spring Integration 4.1中也有
we have promise based gateways notice
我们有基于承诺的网关通知
that when you when you send a message to
当您向您发送消息时
spring integration gateway you get back
您回来的Spring集成网关
a promise so that that runs on
一个承诺，以便继续
unreactive very cool okay interesting
不反应很酷好有趣
all right I didn't thank you I didn't
好吧，我不谢谢你，我没有
realize that on awesome what we're about
意识到，我们真棒
10 minutes after and I think we have
10分钟后，我想我们有
temporarily exhausted the question queue
暂时用尽了问题队列
guys I'm going to give you you know
伙计们，我要给你你知道
there's still like 60 people on the
仍然有60个人
phone I'll give you another minute or
电话，我再给你一分钟或
two to pop in a question while I sort of
我有点想问两个问题
do a quick wrap-up here for us today um
今天在这里为我们做一个快速总结
so I do just want to mention that the
所以我只想提一下
the webinar is being recorded on if you
如果您正在录制网络研讨会，
would like to share the record
想要分享记录
with your colleagues all you need to do
与您的同事所有您需要做的
is subscribe to go to the spring spring
订阅去 Spring
dot IO site and go to the blog spring
点IO网站，并进入The Spring Blog
dot IO forward slash blog on and yeah
点IO正斜杠博客，是的
and then subscribe to the atom feed
然后订阅原子供稿
there and as soon as we get the replay
在那里，一旦我们重播
we always post make a blog post and
我们总是发表博客文章，
embed the YouTube video in the blog post
将YouTube视频嵌入博客文章中
so you'll get a notification that the
因此您会收到一条通知，
replay is available on also by
重播也可以通过
subscribing to the atom feed you get all
订阅原子饲料，您将获得全部
the great blog content from the spring
Spring 的精彩博客内容
engineering group on you know all the
您的工程小组都知道
spring one replays and lots and lots and
春季重播，很多很多，
lots of other great stuff so that's a
还有很多其他很棒的东西
good way to get notified on we always
随时获得通知的好方法
post the link to this slide so um you
将链接发布到此幻灯片，以便您
know Gary will post his slides too
知道加里也将发布他的幻灯片
although there weren't very many
虽然不是很多
dispersor agent ah so maybe I should say
分散剂啊所以也许我应该说
he will post his slide just a few links
他将只发布几个链接来发布他的幻灯片
just a few important links that's all
仅是几个重要的链接
some of the stuff that I looked at the
我看过的一些东西
other thing is you can always on the
另一件事是你可以一直在
blogs you can always you can always
博客你可以永远你可以永远
search for revenue replay given yeah I
搜索收入重播，是的，我
mean you could write it really that's a
就是说你可以写的真的是
good point yeah I really try to be
是的，是的，我真的很想成为
consistent with the naming convention
与命名约定一致
for exactly that reason yep um so we
正是因为这个原因，所以我们
always have that same naming convention
始终具有相同的命名约定
and then so the the replay view would be
然后，重播视图将是
available we usually I usually try to
通常我们通常会尝试
get it done within week or too often
在一周内或过于频繁地完成
much sooner depending on what's crack
快点取决于裂缝
and so on but at the outside you'll see
依此类推，但在外面您会看到
you have the replay in two weeks that
你有两周的重放
you can share with your colleagues and
您可以与您的同事分享，
go back and analyze every word that Gary
回去分析加里的每一个字
and I uttered and call us to the mat for
然后我说出话来叫我们到垫子上
saying something incorrect so um also if
说一些不正确的话，嗯，如果
you want to get the software on we just
您想获得我们的软件
note that we don't really enable we
请注意，我们并未真正启用
disabled direct HTTP downloads for
禁用了以下的直接HTTP下载
spring binaries some time ago just
Spring 二进制文件前一段时间
because maintenance is or Gradle is
因为维护是或Gradle是
really a superior experience if you are
如果您真的是一个很棒的体验
just desperate for HTTP downloads you
只是渴望HTTP下载你
know you're on a military network or
知道您在军事网络中或
you're on a government or clothes
你在政府或衣服上
network or you know you're behind 20
网络，或者您知道自己落后20
layers of proxy servers just go to repo
层代理服务器只是去回购
spring do
Spring 做
that's our artifactory server courtesy
那是我们的人工服务器礼貌
of jay frog and
周杰伦青蛙和
on you can get the HTTP downloads you
您可以获取HTTP下载
need there if you are if you are
如果你在这里就需要那里
desperate but as always please give the
绝望，但一如既往，请给
in give the release of world really
在真正释放世界
curious for your feedback we think this
对您的反馈意见感到好奇，我们认为
is huge for spring integration and just
对于 Spring Integration 而言意义重大，
congratulations to our demand and Gary
祝贺我们的需求和加里
for forgetting this done and give us
忘记了完成并给我们
your feedback at Spring Central um looks
您对Spring Central um的反馈意见
like we had one last question pop in
就像我们最后一个问题突然出现
Gary you okay with with ending on a
加里，您可以以
question trouble okay Eric the guy that
问题麻烦好吧，埃里克，那个家伙，
asked that great question about Adam
问了一个关于亚当的大问题
excuse me about um axon he's curious
对不起，我对他的轴心感到好奇
using what would the difference be
用什么区别
between spring XD plus spring
在Spring XD加Spring 之间
integration and spring batch so this is
集成和Spring Batch处理，所以这是
a softball nice okay well you it
垒球好吧，好吧
actually spring XD I kind of stole a
实际上是 Spring 的XD我有点偷了
little bit of XD thunder by saying that
说一点点XD雷声
spring XD is sort of a based on spring
spring XD是基于spring的
integration it's actually comprised of
整合实际上是由
spring integration and spring batch so
Spring 整合和Spring 批处理
so spring XD as well as having stream
所以 Spring XD以及有流
processing for end to end a data data
端到端数据处理
pipe and transformation etc we also have
管道和改造等，我们也有
the ability to to deploy jobs into
部署作业的能力
spring XD and and so we can do things
Spring XD，所以我们可以做些事情
like launch jobs via spring XD and of
例如通过Spring XD和的发布工作
course the spring batch project itself
当然，Spring Batch处理项目本身
has a module used to be in spring batch
有一个用于Spring Batch处理的模块
admin but this is there's a module in in
管理员，但是这里有一个模块
spring batch called spring batch
Spring Batch称为Spring Batch
integration which actually has the hooks
集成实际上具有挂钩
for doing things like launching a batch
做诸如启动批处理之类的事情
job from a spring integration flow so so
Spring 整合流程中的工作
you can have spring integration flow for
你可以有Spring 集成流程
example that the downloads a file from
从以下位置下载文件的示例
FTP does some work on that file stores
FTP在该文件存储上做了一些工作
the file somewhere else and then
该文件在其他地方，然后
launches a batch job to process that
启动一个批处理作业来处理
file and so that's that's one thing and
文件，那是一回事，
then the other the other direction is
那么另一个方向是
you you can within a spring spring batch
你可以在春季Spring Batch中
job you can launch spring integration
您可以启动Spring集成的工作
flow so so within an item reader or
在物品阅读器内流动或
writer will have you if you need to
如果您需要作家将有您
or an item process if you need to go out
或需要外出的物品处理
you can you can invoke a spring
你可以调用Spring
integration flow from within your spring
从 Spring 开始的整合流程
batch job and there are lots of examples
批处理作业，并且有很多示例
of that in in spring batch project but
在Spring Batch量项目中
but as I said spring XD itself does
但是正如我所说的，Spring XD本身确实
encapsulate jobs and it does a
封装工作，它做一个
particularly good job with the partition
分区特别好
jobs where where it actually uses the XD
实际上使用XD的作业
container infrastructure and zookeeper
集装箱基础设施和动物园管理员
stuff for maintaining instances to
用于维护实例的东西
actually do job partitioning so to start
实际进行工作分区，因此开始
the partition job and launch launch day
分区作业和启动发布日
their launch partitions to be to be
他们的启动分区是
handled in different XD containers and
在不同的XD容器中处理
then the results are all accumulated
然后结果全部累加
back into the partition jobs if you have
返回到分区作业（如果有）
a huge job that needs needs multi
需要大量工作的巨大工作
processing or even multi JVMs to
处理甚至多个JVM
actually get the work done then xtn is
实际完成工作，那么xtn是
another excellent platform for running
另一个出色的跑步平台
such jobs awesome thanks Gary yeah it's
这样的工作太棒了，谢谢Gary是的
just it's funny I got to remind myself
只是很有趣，我要提醒自己
all the time too to really think of XD
一直都在思考XD
is this sort of seamless extension to
是这种无缝扩展
both batch and integration and that you
批处理和集成，您
can't really think or talk about
不能真正思考或谈论
integration in batch anymore without
批量集成，无需
thinking about XD right on and and then
想着XD然后
and that you know regardless you know it
而且你知道，不管你知道什么
is and yet it is some you know just so
是，但是有些你知道
everyone on the phone that realizes you
认识您的电话中的每个人
know it is something a little bit
知道这有点
different right from from traditional
与传统不同的权利
spring libraries that are embeddable in
可嵌入的spring库
your application your spring XD is a
您的应用程序，您的spring XD是
runtime and if you look at our spring
运行时，如果你看看我们的 Spring
Iowa platform diagram I mean this is
爱荷华州平台图，我的意思是
part of the execution layer this is part
执行层的一部分，这是一部分
of the sort of run time you know this
你知道的那种运行时间
concept of domain-specific runtimes that
特定于域的运行时的概念
we've we've been advancing you know so
我们一直在进步，你知道
it's a little bit different from some of
它与某些
your traditional Spring dome projects
您传统的Spring Dome项目
that are just embeddable libraries for
只是可嵌入的库
where this is actually a runtime in a
这实际上是一个
server and because it is you can do some
服务器，因为这是你可以做一些
really fun it can do some really
真的很有趣，它可以做一些真正的
interesting things excuse me so Gary um
有趣的事情对不起，所以Gary um
thank you so much and Artem I know
非常感谢，我知道阿尔Art
you're on the line and then helping out
你在排队，然后帮忙
with a chat just congratulations to both
聊天，恭喜双方
of you this is an absolutely epic
你们这绝对是史诗般的
release and um thank you guys for the
发布，嗯，谢谢你们
for the time that you spent with with us
与您一起度过的时光
today and um yeah
今天和嗯
will will will post a brief lay within a
将会在
week or two any comments you want to
一两周您想发表的任何评论
make to close it out just just usual
像平常一样将其关闭
resources the Stack Overflow with a
资源与堆栈溢出
spring integration tag if you have any
spring集成标签（如果有）
questions you have any new feature
问题，您有任何新功能
suggestions we could start up and spread
我们可以开始传播的建议
Stack Overflow and another progress or
堆栈溢出和其他进度或
just go to the JIRA directly and and ask
直接去JIRA问一下
for asked the spring integration exceed
要求Spring 整合超过
SL is currently managed through the
目前，SL是通过
integration extensions as I mentioned
我提到的集成扩展
it's it's on its own life cycle right
这是它自己的生命周期
now so you can either enter them in the
现在，您可以在
in the in-text project in JIRA or you
在JIRA的文本项目中
can put them in in because as I say
可以放进去，因为正如我所说
eventually it will be it will be folded
最终它将被折叠
into into spring integration problem so
陷入Spring 整合问题
stack overflows to the first place for
堆栈溢出到第一位
questions and such and and the JIRA and
问题等等，JIRA和
of course as Peter mentioned if you keep
当然如彼得所说，如果你继续
an eye on the blog on spring i/o then we
看着 Spring 的博客，然后我们
generally post stuff up there that might
通常在那儿张贴可能
be interesting to the community for sure
对社区肯定很有趣
thank you okay all right thanks everyone
谢谢，好吧，谢谢大家
and have a great day we'll see you the
祝您有个愉快的一天
next webinar if we do have a pretty cool
下一次网络研讨会，如果我们确实很不错
lineup coming up on if your excuse me
如果您不好意思，请参加
next couple webinars are already up on
接下来的几场网络研讨会已经开始
the on the spring site but we've got
在春季现场，但我们有
some good stuff coming up on spring
Spring 来了一些好东西
session on February you should take a
2月的会议上，您应该参加
look at the February lineup some pretty
看二月的阵容
good stuff like it's a spring session
好东西，像是春季会议
we've got a webinar from handy Wilkinson
我们有一个方便的威尔金森网络研讨会
on documenting rest api's talking about
关于记录 rest api 的讨论
you know swagger Alps you know how do
你知道昂首阔步的阿尔卑斯山，你知道怎么做
you how do you deal with the metadata
你如何处理元数据
and one other topic that it's actually
还有一个实际上是主题
escaping remember at the moment but on
逃避此刻，但继续
take a look at Springdale blog if you
看看Springdale博客，如果您
look at this week in spring is usually a
看看这个星期的 Spring 通常是
quick wrap-up of whatever webinars are
任何网络研讨会的快速总结
coming up on so that's always a good
来吧，所以总是很好
place to find them if not just on this
不仅在此找到他们的地方
going through the blog plane-trees
遍历博客平面树
thanks everyone
感谢大家
have a great week see you later bye-bye
祝你有个愉快的一周再见
you
您